http://www.globalinterconnect.com/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
Global Interconnect, Inc. operates https://www.globalinterconnect.com (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing you with information and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”).
This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this information in order to improve the Site as well as our products and services.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and in response to requests for information.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Policy was last changed on September 10, 2019. If Global Interconnect, Inc. makes changes to this Policy, it will be revised so that you always know what information we currently gather, how we might use that information and to whom we may disclose it. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time and without notice and any such changes immediately take effect when posted unless we advise you otherwise. Your continued use of the Services and/or the Site after this Policy has been amended shall constitute your continued acceptance of the terms and conditions of the Policy, as amended. Contact Us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us below.
Contact Us
Fields marked * are requiredName*Organization*I'm Interested In:ExtrusionMoldingStampingMachiningCircuit BoardsAssemblyPackagingSterilizationEmail*
Phone Number*I'm Interested In:ExtrusionMoldingStampingMachiningCircuit BoardsAssemblyPackagingSterilizationWe need help with:Cost ControlEngineering ResourcesLocal Program ManagementManufacturing ScalabilityUninterrupted Supply ChainsPlease tell us a little about your needs:EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Our website uses cookies to personalize and enhance your experience. By continuing without changing your cookie settings, you agree to this collection. For more information, please see our Privacy Policy.Ok
